[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Under what name is the Mr. Clean brand name known in Germany?", "correct_answer": "Meister Proper", "incorrect_answers": ["Mister Sauber", "Herr Steril", "Mr. Wunderbar"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What famous actor and comedian voiced Mushu the Chinese dragon in the 1998 animated movie Mulan?", "correct_answer": "Eddie Murphy", "incorrect_answers": ["Chris Rock", "Chris Tucker", "Will Smith"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which volcano, located on Ross Island, Antarctica, is the southernmost active volcano on Earth?", "correct_answer": "Mount Erebus", "incorrect_answers": ["Mayon Volcano", "Cold Bay Volcano", "Teide"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Fashion designer Alexander McQueen, known as the hooligan of English fashion, succeeded John Galliano as head designer at this French fashion house.", "correct_answer": "Givenchy", "incorrect_answers": ["Chanel", "Christian Lacroix", "Dolce  Gabbana"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If the world were a village of 100 people, how many people would possess 59% of the worlds wealth?", "correct_answer": "6", "incorrect_answers": ["20", "2", "60"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What characters from an animated series, did the cereal Fruity Pebbles feature as its mascot?", "correct_answer": "None of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Daffy Duck and Bugs Bunny", "Tom and Jerry", "Mickey Mouse and Donald Duck"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At what clothing company did Sue Ellen work in the comedy film Dont Tell Mom the Babysitters Dead?", "correct_answer": "GAW (General Apparel West)", "incorrect_answers": ["SAW (Sentimental Apparel West)", "CAW (Clothing Apparel West)", "AAW (Accessories and Apparel West)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Due to the shape of its fruits, Aztecs called this tree Ahuacuatl, which meant testicle tree.", "correct_answer": "Avocado", "incorrect_answers": ["Apple", "Banana", "Pear"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of food do chinchillas prefer to feed on in the wild?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Plants", "Insects", "Fruits"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the character Zack Mallozzis profession in the movie Rat Race?", "correct_answer": "ambulance driver", "incorrect_answers": ["toy dealer", "policeman", "postal worker"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The term clone, originally used in botany before it entered molecular genetics, means what in Greek?", "correct_answer": "Twig", "incorrect_answers": ["Twin", "Copy", "Root"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1985 drama Mask, what was the name of the blind girl Rocky meets at camp?", "correct_answer": "Diana", "incorrect_answers": ["Jesse", "Rusty", "Beth"]}]